CONTACT

- mobile number
- Sydney NSW 2000 AUSTRALIA
- www.irahrosete.com

IRAH ROSETE

Web Developer



(7) /irahrosete



in /irahrosete



/IrahRosete



(ir.dsgns

ABOUT ME

Highly self-motivated and goal-oriented professional committed to a career change in web design and development. Fast-learner with the ability to grasp concepts and new technologies quickly. Offers 10 years of demonstrated history in the financial services industry with strong analytical and problem-solving skills. Lover of design with a desire to create that is guided by order, simplicity, geometry and minimalism.

EDUCATION

- DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Coder Academy 2020-2021
- CERTIFICATE IV IN GRAPHIC DESIGN The Graphic Design School 2019-2020
- CERTIFICATE III IN BUILDING DESIGN TAFE NSW 2018-2019
- DIPLOMA OF FINANCIAL PLANNING Kaplan Professional 2014-2016
- MASTER OF COMMERCE Univesity of New South Wales 2009-2011
- BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS **ADMINISTRATION** University of the Philippines 2002-2006

WORK EXPERIENCE _____

Australia 2020-Present

MACQUARIE BANK

OPERATIONS QUALITY ANALYST

· Conducts quality reviews on operational processes and recommends improvements and efficiency gains

2019-2020

PLATFORM OPERATIONS ADMINISTRATOR

 Provided quality work on account closures for platform products including superannuation, pension, investment and trading accounts

2018-2019

PROPRIETARY PRODUCT ANALYST

 Provided product expertise support through business analysis, process mapping and project management

2017-2018

BUSINESS ANALYST

- · Performed in an Agile and Scrum environment analysing system flows through interviews, workshops and documentation analysis to find solutions to requirements
- Documented test plans and run sheets for systems disaster recovery test
- Facilitated meetings and coordinated the annual review and certification of the trade ordering system with ASX on Market Integrity Rules for submission to ASIC
- · Performed analysis on the migration of insurance clients from a legacy system
- Performed in a DevOps environment supporting production issues relating to trading functionalities and finding ways to enhance the platform

2016-2017

PRODUCT ACCOUNT MANAGER

 Identified impacts of regulatory changes liaising with different teams like IT, Operations, Marketing, Front Office and Legal to ensure compliance of product offerings

PROJECTS

SIP CIDERY

Ø sipcidery.herokuapp.com
 A full-stack web application built on Ruby on Rails for cider makers to showcase their products and cider drinkers to discover new ciders

Frame of Mind

∂ frame-of-mind-60add.web.app

A web app that showcases artworks
from the MET museum API and plays
tunes from the spotify API; product
of a two-day hackathon on Web APIs

Snake Game

∂ github.com/irahrosete/snake-game
A terminal application built on Ruby
replicating the classic snake game

CERTIFICATIONS ____

MICROSOFT EXCEL VBA
Univesrity of Sydney
Centre for Continuing Education
2020

AGILE BUSINESS ANALYSIS (AgileBA®)
FOUNDATION CERTIFICATION
APMG International
PM-Partners Group
2018

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

SYDNEY INTERNATIONAL TENNIS
Court Services Volunteer
2013-2018
Spectator Services Volunteer
2010-2012

UNSW STATIONERY REUSE CENTRE
Publicity Leader
2011

INTERESTS

Graphic Design and Illustration Karate Drums Hiking Architecture

WORK EXPERIENCE

2012-2016

PLATFORM ADMINISTRATOR

- Provided consistent quality work on account opening and maintenance
- Served as change champion in transitioning the team to a new workflow system
- Trained an offshore team and served as the main contact person onshore
- Assisted in the training and development of new and exsiting team members
- Provided appropriate operational cover when team lead is away

2012-2012

ASSOCIATE

 Processed period-end commission payments and interest collections on structured loan products, and implemented improvements on procedures for better control and transparency

Australia 2010-2012

UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES

ADMINSTRATIVE ASSISTANT

 Collated vital data and maintained repository of approved university research materials for submission to Australian Research Council

Philippines 2006-2009

DEUTSCHE BANK

ASSOCIATE

 Migrated and maintained P&L, balance sheet and trade processes from Sydney and London to the Manila operations

TECH STACK ____

ਰ HTML

∃ CSS

Js JavaScript

React

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

◆ Git

អ Heroku

aws AWS S3

PostgreSQL

Jira J

X Confluence

Salesforce

